Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
Welcome to the Night King City auction.
مرحباً بكم في مزاد Night King City.
We hope everyone bids enthusiastically.
نأمل أن يشارك الجميع بحماس.
Thank you for your support.
شكرا لدعمكم.
The auction officially begins now.
يبدأ المزاد رسميًا الآن.
The first item up for auction
العنصر الأول المعروض للبيع بالمزاد
is this piece of Glow Pearl Stone.
هذه القطعة من حجر اللؤلؤ المتوهج.
Starting bid is 100,000 Glow Pearls.
السعر الابتدائي هو 100000 لؤلؤة متوهجة.
500,000.
500,000.
I'll bid to support Xiao Yue.
سأقدم عرضًا لدعم شياو يوي.
Raise the bid.
رفع العرض.
1,500,000.
1,500,000.
2,000,000.
2,000,000.
5,000,000.
5,000,000.
Lin Yue.
لين يو.
Are you out of your mind?
هل أنت خارج عقلك؟
5,000,000, going once.
5,000,000، مرة واحدة.
5,000,000, going twice.
5,000,000، الذهاب مرتين.
5,000,000, going three times.
5,000,000، ثلاث مرات.
Sold!
مُباع!
Five million for a useless rock?
خمسة ملايين مقابل صخرة عديمة الفائدة؟
Let's see how you explain this to the Sect.
دعونا نرى كيف تشرح هذا للطائفة.
Let me show you something impressive.
دعني أريك شيئًا مثيرًا للإعجاب.
This stone is made of Mystic Silver.
هذا الحجر مصنوع من الفضة الصوفية.
It's worth five million on its own.
إنها تساوي خمسة ملايين بمفردها.
Not to mention,
ناهيك عن ذلك،
Look closely!
أنظر عن كثب!
A talisman!
تعويذة!
Besides,
بجانب،
Inside this Mystic Silver,
داخل هذا الفضة الغامضة،
there's a top-tier talisman.
هناك تعويذة من الدرجة الأولى.
It's one of a kind in the entire Hongmeng Continent.
إنه فريد من نوعه في قارة هونغ مينغ بأكملها.
This talisman
هذه التعويذة
can be used for the Instant Universe Array.
يمكن استخدامها لمجموعة الكون الفورية.
It allows instant teleportation anywhere.
إنه يسمح بالانتقال الفوري إلى أي مكان.
Looks like Brother Lin is determined to get this talisman.
يبدو أن الأخ لين مصمم على الحصول على هذه التعويذة.
It's good to have it for emergencies.
من الجيد أن يكون لدينا ذلك لحالات الطوارئ.
The second auction item
العنصر الثاني للمزاد
is an Ancient Divine Sword.
هو سيف إلهي قديم.
A master craftsman spent thirty years
أمضى أحد الحرفيين ماهرًا ثلاثين عامًا
forging it from Starmetal.
صُنع من معدن النجوم.
Its power is incredible.
قوتها لا تصدق.
Starting bid is one million Glow Pearls.
العرض الأولي هو مليون لؤلؤة متوهجة.
Six million.
ستة ملايين.
Seven million.
سبعة ملايين.
Eight million.
ثمانية ملايين.
Ten million.
عشرة ملايين.
You again?
انت مرة اخرى؟
Twenty million.
عشرون مليون.
Young Master, calm down.
سيدي الشاب، اهدأ.
Fine.
بخير.
We'll buy this sword another time.
سوف نشتري هذا السيف مرة أخرى.
With your skills,
مع مهاراتك،
stop pretending to be rich.
توقف عن التظاهر بأنك غني.
Wait.
انتظر.
Brother Lin,
الأخ لين،
just keep bidding.
فقط استمر في المزايدة.
I'll cover the money.
سأغطي المال.
I'll pay for it.
سأدفع ثمنها.
I appreciate your kindness, Brother Qin.
أقدر لطفك، الأخ تشين.
But
لكن
there's no need
ليست هناك حاجة
to argue with that idiot.
للنقاش مع هذا الأحمق.
The auction has just started.
لقد بدأ المزاد للتو.
We should save our strength.
ينبغي علينا أن نحافظ على قوتنا.
You're the idiot.
أنت أحمق.
Twenty million, going once.
عشرون مليونًا، مرة واحدة.
Twenty million, going twice.
عشرون مليونًا، يذهب مرتين.
Twenty million, going three times.
عشرون مليونًا، ثلاث مرات.
Sold!
مُباع!
Alright, alright!
حسناً حسناً!
Young Master Lei is so cool!
السيد الشاب لي رائع جدًا!
Xiao Yue,
شياو يو,
do you see my strength now?
هل ترى قوتي الآن؟
This Fairy Sword requires weapon bonding.
يتطلب هذا السيف الخيالي ربط السلاح.
Someone like you
شخص مثلك
probably can't even draw it.
ربما لا أستطيع حتى رسمه.
Fairy Sword.
سيف الجنية.
Young Master Lei, you don't know?
السيد الشاب لي، ألا تعلم؟
I bought this sword
لقد اشتريت هذا السيف
to give to our Sect Leader Qin Ji.
لإهدائها إلى زعيم طائفتنا تشين جي.
It's a gift.
إنها هدية.
Why did you buy this sword?
لماذا اشتريت هذا السيف؟
I'm so handsome,
أنا وسيم جداً
how dare you mess with me!
كيف تجرؤ على العبث معي!
You were the one who bid.
لقد كنت الشخص الذي قدم العرض.
How can you blame Young Master Lin?
كيف يمكنك إلقاء اللوم على السيد الشاب لين؟
Young Master,
السيد الشاب،
let him go.
دعوه يذهب.
You can't beat him anyway.
لا يمكنك التغلب عليه على أية حال.
Let go of me!
أتركني!
The third auction item
العنصر الثالث للمزاد
is the treasured artifact of Night King City.
هي قطعة أثرية ثمينة من مدينة ملك الليل.
The Ancient Secret Key.
المفتاح السري القديم.
That's it.
هذا كل شيء.
Starting bid: twenty million Glow Pearls.
سعر البدء: عشرون مليون لؤلؤة متوهجة.
This is Night King City's heirloom.
هذه هي إرث مدينة ملك الليل.
There's a way to keep it from leaving the family.
هناك طريقة لمنعه من مغادرة العائلة.
Whoever wins the treasure
من يفوز بالكنز
will marry Ye Mingyue.
سوف يتزوج من Ye Mingyue.
If the treasure goes to the son-in-law,
إذا ذهب الكنز إلى صهره،
it's not considered passing it to outsiders.
لا يعتبر نقلها إلى الغرباء.
Brother Lin,
الأخ لين،
do you know the origin of this key?
هل تعرف أصل هذا المفتاح؟
Of course I do.
بالطبع أفعل.
And
و
I also know how to use it.
وأنا أعرف أيضًا كيفية استخدامه.
Luo Yixue,
لو ييشوي,
place a bid.
وضع عرض.
How much?
كم ثمن؟
Twenty-five million.
خمسة وعشرون مليونًا.
We don't have that much money, do we?
ليس لدينا الكثير من المال، أليس كذلك؟
Just bid as I say.
فقط قم بالعرض كما أقول.
Twenty-five million.
خمسة وعشرون مليونًا.
I may not know how to use it,
ربما لا أعرف كيفية استخدامه،
but Night King City's treasure
لكن كنز مدينة ملك الليل
can't end up in the hands of a country bumpkin.
لا يمكن أن ينتهي الأمر في أيدي قروي ريفي.
Thirty million.
ثلاثين مليون.
Forty million.
أربعين مليون.
Fifty million.
خمسين مليون.
Sixty million.
ستين مليون.
Sev—
بالنسبة لي—
Sixty-one million.
واحد وستون مليون.
Eighty million.
ثمانون مليون.
Show us your eighty million first.
أرنا الثمانين مليونًا الخاصة بك أولاً.
If you can't,
إذا لم تتمكن من ذلك،
that's fraud.
هذا احتيال.
I'll pay for him.
سأدفع ثمنه.
Sect Leader.
زعيم الطائفة.
So,
لذا،
you really know how to use this key, huh?
هل تعرف حقًا كيفية استخدام هذا المفتاح، أليس كذلك؟
Thank you, Sect Leader.
شكرا لك يا زعيم الطائفة.
Of course I do.
بالطبع أفعل.
There are too many people and eyes here.
هناك الكثير من الناس والعيون هنا.
How about
ماذا عن
we find a quiet place to talk?
نجد مكانًا هادئًا للتحدث؟
I'll follow your arrangements.
سأتبع ترتيباتك.
Discussing such an important secret,
مناقشة مثل هذا السر المهم،
how could you leave out the Young Sect Leader?
كيف يمكنك ترك زعيم الطائفة الشابة خارجًا؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Lin Yue,
لين يو,
you stole my woman and cheated me out of money.
لقد سرقت امرأتي وخدعتني وسرقت أموالي.
Now you're stealing my spotlight.
الآن أنت تسرق الأضواء مني.
I'm settling all scores with you.
أنا أسوي جميع الحسابات معك.
Lei Zong,
لي زونغ,
don't be so arrogant.
لا تكن مغرورًا جدًا.
Your sect's swapping of the Saintess
طائفتك تستبدل القديسة
can't be hidden from me.
لا يمكن إخفاؤه عني.
Jun Wushang,
جون وشانغ,
you sold the city's treasure to an outsider.
لقد بعت كنز المدينة لشخص من الخارج.
What right do you have to lecture me?
ما هو الحق الذي لديك لتحاضرني؟
Today, I insist on killing him.
واليوم أصر على قتله.
Young Sect Leader!
زعيم الطائفة الشاب!
The Sect Leader of Lei Yun Sect is as strong as Jun Wushang.
زعيم طائفة لي يون قوي مثل جون ووشانغ.
If his son is killed,
إذا قُتل ابنه،
this kid won't live much longer.
هذا الطفل لن يعيش لفترة أطول.
He's gotten himself into big trouble.
لقد أدخل نفسه في مشكلة كبيرة.
Father, you saw it all.
أبي، لقد رأيت كل شيء.
Young Master Lin was forced to fight back.
أُرغم الشاب السيد لين على القتال.
I saw everything.
لقد رأيت كل شئ.
But
لكن
Sect Leader Lei definitely won't let this go.
من المؤكد أن زعيم الطائفة لي لن يسمح بهذا الأمر.
Even without this incident,
حتى بدون هذا الحادث،
Lei Yun Sect Leader Lei Long
زعيم طائفة لي يون لي لونغ
would come for us anyway.
سوف يأتي إلينا على أية حال.
Young Master Lin,
السيد الشاب لين،
you should leave Night King City quickly.
ينبغي عليك مغادرة مدينة ملك الليل بسرعة.
You've already got what you wanted.
لقد حصلت بالفعل على ما تريد.
No rush.
لا تستعجل.
There's something I truly want
هناك شيء أريده حقًا
still to come.
لا يزال قادمًا.
You're pretty calm, aren't you?
أنت هادئ جدًا، أليس كذلك؟
Aren't you afraid Lei Long will come for you?
ألا تخاف أن يأتي لي لونغ إليك؟
I'm not someone who fears trouble.
أنا لست من الأشخاص الذين يخافون المتاعب.
You really don't know your limits.
أنت حقا لا تعرف حدودك.
Do you know Lei Yun Sect Leader Lei Long's level?
هل تعرف مستوى زعيم طائفة لي يون لي لونغ؟
Ninth Rotation Realm.
عالم الدوران التاسع.
And you're only at the Salvation Realm.
وأنت فقط في عالم الخلاص.
He could kill you easily.
بإمكانه أن يقتلك بسهولة.
I'm no match for him.
أنا لا أستطيع مواجهته.
But
لكن
I have help.
لقد حصلت على مساعدة.
What help?
ما هي المساعدة؟
Heaven's secrets must not be revealed.
لا ينبغي الكشف عن أسرار السماء.
Sect Leader Ye,
زعيم الطائفة يي،
you came
لقد أتيت
for the Annihilation Cosmic Staff, right?
لطاقم الفناء الكوني، أليس كذلك؟
Except for this kid,
باستثناء هذا الطفل،
everyone else, step back.
الجميع، تراجعوا إلى الوراء.
Step back.
تراجع إلى الوراء.
Yes.
نعم.
You're still so young,
أنت لا تزال صغيرا جدا،
how do you know about the Annihilation Cosmic Staff?
كيف تعرف عن عصا الفناء الكونية؟
The Annihilation Cosmic Staff
طاقم الإبادة الكوني
was left by one of the Three Emperors of the Upper Realm,
وقد تركها أحد الأباطرة الثلاثة في العالم العلوي،
Qi Tian Emperor.
الإمبراطور تشي تيان.
It has the power to sweep through armies.
لديه القدرة على اجتياح الجيوش.
Rumor has it
الاشاعة تتضمن هذا
the Annihilation Cosmic Staff is hidden somewhere in Night King City,
تم إخفاء عصا الفناء الكونية في مكان ما في مدينة ملك الليل،
protected by a mysterious magic array.
محمي بواسطة مجموعة سحرية غامضة.
And your family
و عائلتك
has held the key to the array for generations.
لقد احتفظت بمفتاح المجموعة لأجيال.
But even you
ولكن حتى أنت
don't know the exact location of the array.
لا أعرف الموقع الدقيق للمصفوفة.
So you used the auction
لقد استخدمت المزاد
to lure those in the know.
لجذب أولئك الذين يعرفون.
My daughter was right about you.
ابنتي كانت على حق بشأنك.
Son-in-law, let's head to the array now.
صهرنا، دعنا نتوجه إلى المصفوفة الآن.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
But
لكن
I hope City Lord Ye will agree to one thing.
أتمنى أن يوافق سيد المدينة يي على شيء واحد.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
After we get the Annihilation Cosmic Staff,
بعد أن حصلنا على عصا الفناء الكونية،
I want to borrow it for a while.
أريد استعارته لفترة من الوقت.
To accomplish something important.
لإنجاز شيء مهم.
Once it's done,
بمجرد الانتهاء من ذلك،
I will definitely return it.
سأرجعه بالتأكيد.
Who did this
من فعل هذا؟
with such cruelty?
بهذه القسوة؟
It was Lin Yue.
لقد كان لين يوي.
If I don't avenge this grudge,
إذا لم أنتقم من هذا الحقد،
I swear I won't rest until I get revenge.
أقسم أنني لن أرتاح حتى أنتقم.